ifscswiftcodes.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy - IFSCswiftcodes.com

Effective as of May 25, 2018 (the "Effective Date").

## 1\. Introduction

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in Ifsc swift codes collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the https://ifscswiftcodes.com website. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, and we will notify you of any material changes to the policy by posting the modified policy at Privacy Policy and changing the Effective Date at the top. We encourage you to check this page periodically for any changes. By using or navigating Ifsc swift codes's web site located at https://ifscswiftcodes.com, you acknowledge that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound by this policy or any modified policy as posted.If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use or access our website. 

## 2\. What information is collected?

### 2.1 Log Files

Like many other websites, Ifsc swift codes (ifscswiftcodes.com) makes use of server side log files. The information inside the log files includes information like internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, date/time stamp, referring/exit pages used to analyze and administer the site. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. Ifsc swift codes does not disclose this information publicly or with any third party as it's purpose is intended for aggregate system usage statistics, security investigation and abuse prevention of the service. 

### 2.2.1 ANALYTICS (third-parties)

### Google Analytics with Anonymized IP (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.This integration of Google Analytics anonymizes your IP address. It works by shortening Users' IP addresses within member states of the European Union or in other contracting states to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the complete IP address be sent to a Google server and shortened within the US. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

### 2.2.2 ADVERTISING (third-parties)

This type of services allows User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on this website, possibly based on user interests.This does not mean that personal data is used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below.Some of the services listed below may use Cookies to identify Users or they may use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the user’s interests and behavior, including those detected outside this website. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services. 

### Google Adsense (Google Inc.)

Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of this website and user behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [Opt Out](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en) Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) – [Opt Out](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en)

**Within the European Economic Area (EEA):** This website displays only non-personalized advertisements through the Google AdSense services from Google, Inc.. AdSense will display contextual ads based on the page content of the website you’re visiting or based on location from a variety of sources. The cookies used by AdSense are there to allow for frequency capping (not showing you the same ads repeatedly), aggregated ad reporting (statistics), and to combat fraud and abuse. Please refer to [How Google uses information from sites or apps that use our services](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites) for details.   

### 2.2.3 Content performance and features testing (A/B testing) (third-parties)

The services contained in this section allow the owner to track and analyze the user response concerning web traffic or behavior regarding changes to the structure, text or any other component of this website. Google Website Optimizer (Google Inc.) Google Website Optimizer is an A/B testing service provided by Google Inc. Google may use Personal Data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=policies). Privacy Shield participant.

## 3\. Does this website use cookies?

Yes. "Cookies" are pieces of information (actually, alphanumeric identifiers) generated by web servers and stored in your computer for future access. Cookies cannot view or retrieve data from other cookies, nor can they capture files or data stored on your computer. We, our partners, and our suppliers use cookie technology to enhance your online experience by making it easier for you to navigate through our website or make a feature work better. Generally, cookies can be disabled. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. If you would like to use this website, you may do so without accepting cookies. However, you should understand that if you choose not to accept cookies, some areas of the website may not function properly or optimally and you will not be permitted to access certain secured areas of the website. For more information on cookies, see: <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/faqs/cookie-file.html> By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Ifsc swift codes's use of cookies. 

## 4\. Does this website use web beacons?

Yes. "Web beacons" (also known as "web bugs") are small images, generally a single transparent pixel, served to you as part of a web page or other document. Web beacons may be used in parts of our website for purposes such as site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising auditing and reporting, and personalization. These beacons do not collect personally identifiable information, and do not transfer any personally identifiable information to third parties. If beacons are used by any of our advertising services suppliers, that supplier's privacy policy governs their use. Please see the section "ADVERTISING" above for a list of advertisers and policies. For more information on web beacons, see: <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/faqs/beacons.html>

## 5\. Links To External Sites

Users may find advertising or other content on our site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. 

## 6\. Secure Communications

This site is only loaded over an encrypted connection with the server (HTTPS) providing added protection against surveillance and interference by third-parties. 

## 7\. Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Ifsc swift codes may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Ifsc swift codes’s sole discretion. Ifsc swift codes encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

## 8\. Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via our contact page at: [Contact us](https://www.ifscswiftcodes.com/Contact-us/Feedback.php)
